Hugo W. Miller papers, 1902-1958
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Hugo W. Miller papers, 1902-1958
AZ 175
Miller, Hugo Walter
Assay and ore records, and miscellaneous financial and administrative papers. Includes mill, smelter, and convertor reports for the Pride of the West Mining and Milling Company for 1902.
5 linear l feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL:http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Businessman and engineer, Nogales, Arizona. Began Miller's Assay Office in 1913; later Miller and Cox, 1921- 1924, later Hugo W. Miller Assay Office, 1924-1958.
Organization
This collection is organized into two series:
Series I: Personal and Financial Materials, 1902-1952
Series II: Ore and Assay Records, 1913-1958
Scope and Content Note
Assay and ore records, and miscellaneous financial and administrative papers. Includes mill, smelter, and convertor reports for the Pride of the West Mining and Milling Company for 1902.
Access Terms
Miller and Cox Assay Office -- Records and correspondence
Pride of the West Mining and Milling Company -- Records and correspondence
Mines and mineral resources -- Arizona -- History -- Sources
Assaying -- History -- Sources
Assayers -- Arizona -- Archives
Account Books
Journals (bookkeeping)
Container List
- Series I: Personal and Financial Papers, 1902-1937
  - Miscellaneous Personal and Financial Papers. 1902-1937 (Volume 1)
  - Monthly and Six-Month Business Summary. 1915-1921 (Volume 2)
  - Monthly Business Summary. 1921-1923 (Volume 3)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records (rents, loans, leftover assay accounts, payrolls, personal notes, retail sales). 1923-1925 (Volume 4)
  - Cash Accounts. 1924-1927 (Volume 5)
  - Various Ore Tests (mill, smelter and converter reports of the Pride of the West Mining and Milling Company). 1923-1924 (Volume 6)
  - Daily Journal (includes inventory of the Assay Office). 1933-1934 (Volume 7)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records (assaying, loans, labor, contracts, shipments). 1937 (Volume 8)
- Series II: Ore and Assay Records, 1913-1958
  - Ore Records. 1913-1928 (Volume 9)
  - Ore Records. 1928-1943 (Volume 10)
  - Assay Records. 1913-1917 (Volume 11)
  - Assay Records. 1917-1918 (Volume 12)
  - Assay Records. 1918 (Volume 13)
  - Assay Records. 1918-1920 (Volume 14)
  - Assay Records. 1920-1921 (Volume 15)
  - Assay Records. 1921-1923 (Volume 16)
  - Assay Records. 1924-1925 (Volume 17)
  - Assay Records. 1926-1929 (Volume 18)
  - Assay Records. 1930-1932 (Volume 19)
  - Assay Records. 1933-1934 (Volume 20)
  - Assay Records. 1935-1938 (Volume 21)
  - Assay Records. 1938-1943 (Volume 22)
  - Assay Records. 1943-1949 (Volume 23)
  - Assay Records. 1950-1958 (Volume 24)